fireupnow.biz 2012-05-01

# Privacy « Fire Up Your Business

PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated: January 6th, 2010

FireUpNow.biz strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet  
technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may  
use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street  
address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will  
never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party.  
Period.”

How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the  
activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For  
example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access  
to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or  
when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate  
in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other  
interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, FireUpNow.biz also collects  
information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be  
transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet  
Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information  
from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and  
password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you  
visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular  
advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may  
also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose  
not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse  
to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of  
the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may  
not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.  
What we do with the information we collect.

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and  
deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and  
do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may  
be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your  
usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help  
enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or  
what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be  
shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does  
not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to  
identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on FireUpNow.biz to  
communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences;  
our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by  
FireUpNow.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by FireUpNow.biz may also be  
used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration,  
troubleshooting, processing of ecommerce transactions, administration of  
sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third  
parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web  
hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your  
information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we  
continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other  
companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among  
the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a  
court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so  
by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to  
law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary.  
Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.  
Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements.

FireUpNow.biz expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the  
privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our  
partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through  
our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.  
For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a  
frame on a FireUpNow.biz page, certain content that is actually created or  
hosted by a third party. Also, through FireUpNow.biz you may be introduced to,  
or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes  
offered by other parties. FireUpNow.biz is not responsible for the actions or  
policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of  
those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a  
third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may  
use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences  
or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served  
by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine  
whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features  
available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use  
cookies or other technology to gather information. FireUpNow.biz does not  
control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and  
is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable  
Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed  
publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge  
and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.  
Such activities are beyond the control of FireUpNow.biz and this policy.

Children

FireUpNow.biz does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable  
Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we  
discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of  
this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe  
FireUpNow.biz has any information from or about anyone under 13, please  
contact us at the address listed below.

Contacting Us.

We can be reached by contacting:  
Email: info(at)fireupnow.biz

Changes to this Policy

FireUpNow.biz reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please  
check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following  
the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.  
Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used  
according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was  
collected.

Governing law

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by California law. If a dispute  
arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a  
mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: California. Any costs  
and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared  
equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through  
mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following  
location: California, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association.  
Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any  
court with jurisdiction to do so. FireUpNow.biz is controlled, operated and  
administered entirely within California. This statement and the policies outlined  
herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights  
in or on behalf of any party.
